[
    {
        "front": "apple",
        "back": "Apfel"
    },
    {
        "front": "house",
        "back": "Haus"
    },
    {
        "front": "car",
        "back": "Auto"
    },
    {
        "front": "tree",
        "back": "Baum"
    },
    {
        "front": "water",
        "back": "Wasser"
    },
    {
        "front": "bread",
        "back": "Brot"
    },
    {
        "front": "sun",
        "back": "Sonne"
    },
    {
        "front": "moon",
        "back": "Mond"
    },
    {
        "front": "book",
        "back": "Buch"
    },
    {
        "front": "flower",
        "back": "Blume"
    }
]
